<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Drupal on Bargav Kondapu</title>
    <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/categories/drupal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Drupal on Bargav Kondapu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 16:00:42 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bargavkondapu.com/categories/drupal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Drupal 7 Migrate Taxonomy to Organic Groups</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/projects/drupal-7-migrate-taxonomy-to-organic-groups/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 16:00:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/projects/drupal-7-migrate-taxonomy-to-organic-groups/</guid>
      <description>Organic Groups module for drupal, enable users to create and manage their own &amp;lsquo;groups&amp;rsquo;. Each group can have subscribers, and maintains a group home page where subscribers communicate amongst themselves.
A website of a federal client, that I worked on, had custom groups functionality, implemented using taxonomy. It became out-of-scale to manage that way, any longer and also they with restricted, by that. This module, crawls through each taxonomy term, create an organic group, based on those terms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drupal 7 Tags Cleanup</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/projects/drupal-7-tags-cleanup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 16:00:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/projects/drupal-7-tags-cleanup/</guid>
      <description>One of the problems, user&amp;rsquo;s face is too-many similar tags. Since tags can be created by multiple people, there is a posiblity of two users, creating same tag, with a minor difference.
For example, informationTechnology, Information Technology, Information-Technology, information technology,&amp;hellip; are all valid tags and mean the same. When a user wants to tag a content, they often gets confused with which tag to use.
This module, is created as a drush command, scans through such tags, identify which one to keep and deletes other tags.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acquisition Gateway GSA</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/projects/acquisition-gateway-gsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 15:09:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/projects/acquisition-gateway-gsa/</guid>
      <description>The Acquisition Gateway is your workspace for acquisition professionals and federal buyers to connect with resources, tools and each other to improve acquisition government-wide.
This website is built in Drupal 7 and AngularJS, in a progress decoupled architecture. Aside from regular updates and changes, I have enhanced search functionality, developed custom modules to remove duplicate taxonomy and to create organic groups based on taxonomy.
Project URL: https://hallways.cap.gsa.gov
Technologies Used : Drupal, Apache Solr, Github, Amazon AWS, AngularJS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FirstNet</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/projects/firstnet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2017 14:53:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/projects/firstnet/</guid>
      <description>The FirstNet mission is to deploy, operate, maintain, and improve the first high-speed, nationwide wireless broadband network dedicated to public safety.
This website is front facing , first step for the experience. It is implemented in drupal8, using panels and layout modules. This site is robust, secure and 508 Accessibility Compliant.
Project URL: https://www.firstnet.com/
Technologies Used : Drupal, Jenkins, Acquia, Amazon AWS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Architectural Adventures</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/projects/architectural-adventures/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2016 14:32:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/projects/architectural-adventures/</guid>
      <description>Architectural Adventures is the official travel program of The American Institute of Architects, offering first-rate experiences in breathtaking destinations across the globe.
This is implemented during my job at AIA. It follows the same architecture and principles as that of the the previous project.
Project URL: https://www.architecturaladventures.org/
Technologies Used : Drupal, EmberJS, NodeJs, ElasticSearch, Travis-CI, Github, Amazon AWS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The American Institure of Architects</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/projects/the-american-institure-of-architects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2016 14:00:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/projects/the-american-institure-of-architects/</guid>
      <description>The American Institute of Architects is a professional organization for architects in the United States. I feel privileged to work for this organization. As a web developer there, from 2015-2016, we built this website, using Drupal 8 and EmberJS.
This project is one of early adopters of &amp;lsquo;Progressive Decoupled&amp;rsquo; architecture. We made use Drupal8&amp;rsquo;s REST API and Ember Datastore and Ember fastboot to achieve this.
Project URL: https://www.aia.org/
Technologies Used : Drupal, EmberJS, NodeJs, ElasticSearch, Travis-CI, Github, Amazon AWS.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>