<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bargav Kondapu</title>
    <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Bargav Kondapu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2020 14:32:06 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bargavkondapu.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A note from Bargav</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-37/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2020 14:32:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-37/</guid>
      <description> “If you want to be happy, be.” -Leo Tolstoy
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A note from Bargav</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-36/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2020 04:05:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-36/</guid>
      <description>Dream!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If By Rudyard Kipling</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/posts/if-by-rudyard-kipling/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 08:48:53 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/posts/if-by-rudyard-kipling/</guid>
      <description>I read this as a teen and never felt so inspired. I still keep reading to keep myself inspired.
 If you can keep your head when all about you
Are losing theirs and blaming it on you;
If you can trust yourself when all men doubt you,
But make allowance for their doubting too;
If you can wait and not be tired by waiting,
Or being lied about, don’t deal in lies,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactions of B</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 12:36:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-20/</guid>
      <description>Would you be incredibly stupid, but lucky or incredibly genius, but unlucky? Interaction with 3 kids that my wife was babysitting. They were watching some random game reviewer’s video, where he was asking different ‘what would you choose?’ questions and showing polls of what other people chose afterwards.
One of the question is “Would you be incredibly stupid, but lucky or be incredibly genius, but unlucky?”
Kid 1: What question is that, of course I would choose genius.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Problem With Fake News in Digital Marketing</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/posts/problem-with-fake-news-in-digital-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 12:03:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/posts/problem-with-fake-news-in-digital-marketing/</guid>
      <description>I was scrolling through my news feed, and shocked at what I found.
First, It was a story about a news paper vendor that helped Bill Gates when he doesn&amp;rsquo;t have money. - Fake
Next, It was a story about an interaction between JRD Tata and Amitabh - Fake.
Then, another couple of posts describing interactions where either candidates outsmarted interviewers or employees outsmarted their bosses. - Fake  Followed by a question of &amp;ldquo;what do you think?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A note from Bargav</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-35/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 21:48:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-35/</guid>
      <description>The Hulk is confused. Help him choose which side, he should step in.
A concept shoot, inspired from the conflict of decisions we face every single day.
Your life is not defined by one big decision. It is defined by small decisions you make over and over again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A note from Bargav</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-34/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 20:36:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-34/</guid>
      <description>Change happens, not when you change, but when you be yourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactions of B</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Dec 2018 21:28:48 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-19/</guid>
      <description>I was talking to a 5 yr old girl, X and asked her to tell a story, while she is sketching
X - Drew 3 figures on a paper, started speaking, pointing to them :
This is a princess, and this is her mean step mom. She used to trouble princess. This is prince. They both killed their mean step mom and lived happily.
Me : Oh that’s good. Can you tell another one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Rules for Profitable Self Discipline</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/posts/10-rules-for-profitable-self-discipline/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 23:10:40 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/posts/10-rules-for-profitable-self-discipline/</guid>
      <description>It was a sunday evening and we were discussing random topics among our friends. One of the topics that came up, was on how to communicate effectively? or more precisely, how to discuss crucial topics, without either one being offended. This discussion, reminded me of an old yet, timeless speech by Napoleon Hill on 10 Rules for Profitable Self Discipline.
The 10 Rules for Profitable self discipline are
1. Keep cool when others get hot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A note from Bargav</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-33/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2018 22:02:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-33/</guid>
      <description>“I am not who you think I am.
I am not who I think I am.
I am who I think you think I am ” -Thomas Cooley
 Read it multiple times to understand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A note from Bargav</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-32/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Apr 2018 22:02:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-32/</guid>
      <description>You realize that your brain is off, when you order Chikni Chameli, instead of Chiken Panini.
#facepalmmoment #insomnia</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Haveli Bistro</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/projects/haveli-bistro/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 01:43:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/projects/haveli-bistro/</guid>
      <description>Haveli bistro is an upscale Indian restaurant, in Down Town Columbus, Ohio.
I have worked on branding and development of the website. Website is built and hosted in DUDA professional webbuilder.
Project URL: https://www.havelibistro.com/
Technologies Used : Duda,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A note from Bargav</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Mar 2018 22:02:28 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-31/</guid>
      <description>A vision is like a dream. It will disappear unless we do something with it. Do something big or do something small. But stop wandering and go on with an adventure.
- From Simon Sinek&amp;rsquo;s little book of inspiration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A note from Bargav</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 21:59:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-30/</guid>
      <description>The most powerful force in the human psychic is how we describe ourselves to ourself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A note from Bargav</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-29/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 21:59:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-29/</guid>
      <description>Your life is not defined by one big decision. It is defined by small decisions you make over and over again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A note from Bargav</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-28/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2018 21:59:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-28/</guid>
      <description>Einstein theorized and we all agree that E=mc², where E, m and c represents energy, mass and the speed of light respectively.
E, m and c are not almighty that come and solve your problems. They are just an arbitrary representations used to explain a theory.
Same is with Shiva, Vishnu, Jesus, Allah, Durga&amp;hellip; and all 1 million+ gods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactions of B</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 19:34:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-18/</guid>
      <description>An interaction with Mr. X, Doctor by profession and a Social worker by heart, at the airport waiting for our flight. Discussing ways to empower people from remote/ backward areas
Me: So why do you think the majority of the people that are hunger-stricken or poor unable to think big?
X: Okay! Tell me are you a &amp;lsquo;Glass is half-full&amp;rsquo; person or &#39; Glass is half-empty&#39; person?
Me: &amp;lsquo;Half-full&amp;rsquo; may be!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactions of B</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 19:36:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-17/</guid>
      <description>Wrong type of Audience! This interaction has got me thinking for a long time, and would like to know more of your thoughts on this.
Me: So what do you think is the problem with helpful articles, inspirations or advices on social media.
X: There is no problem with those articles, but the problem is with such articles reaching wrong audience. and people being inspired from sources that are not relevant to them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A note from Bargav</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 21:55:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-27/</guid>
      <description>A Wealth Of Information Creates A Poverty Of Attention</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drupal 7 Migrate Taxonomy to Organic Groups</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/projects/drupal-7-migrate-taxonomy-to-organic-groups/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 16:00:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/projects/drupal-7-migrate-taxonomy-to-organic-groups/</guid>
      <description>Organic Groups module for drupal, enable users to create and manage their own &amp;lsquo;groups&amp;rsquo;. Each group can have subscribers, and maintains a group home page where subscribers communicate amongst themselves.
A website of a federal client, that I worked on, had custom groups functionality, implemented using taxonomy. It became out-of-scale to manage that way, any longer and also they with restricted, by that. This module, crawls through each taxonomy term, create an organic group, based on those terms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drupal 7 Tags Cleanup</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/projects/drupal-7-tags-cleanup/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 16:00:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/projects/drupal-7-tags-cleanup/</guid>
      <description>One of the problems, user&amp;rsquo;s face is too-many similar tags. Since tags can be created by multiple people, there is a posiblity of two users, creating same tag, with a minor difference.
For example, informationTechnology, Information Technology, Information-Technology, information technology,&amp;hellip; are all valid tags and mean the same. When a user wants to tag a content, they often gets confused with which tag to use.
This module, is created as a drush command, scans through such tags, identify which one to keep and deletes other tags.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactions of B</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 19:34:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-16/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t usually get offended or irritated, but interactions like these, make me feel uncomfortable.
As you might already know, we are establishing a web-development firm and is currently looking for more projects. Met X, who is opening a new shop and called me to discuss his branding and development needs.
&amp;hellip;
After a lengthy discussion on how we can improve his shop&amp;rsquo;s digital footprint.
X: So, how much would you charge?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A note from Bargav</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 21:03:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-26/</guid>
      <description>There are always 3 sides to an argument. Your side, other side and the right side, which is usually in middle of the two sides.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acquisition Gateway GSA</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/projects/acquisition-gateway-gsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 15:09:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/projects/acquisition-gateway-gsa/</guid>
      <description>The Acquisition Gateway is your workspace for acquisition professionals and federal buyers to connect with resources, tools and each other to improve acquisition government-wide.
This website is built in Drupal 7 and AngularJS, in a progress decoupled architecture. Aside from regular updates and changes, I have enhanced search functionality, developed custom modules to remove duplicate taxonomy and to create organic groups based on taxonomy.
Project URL: https://hallways.cap.gsa.gov
Technologies Used : Drupal, Apache Solr, Github, Amazon AWS, AngularJS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactions of B</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 19:34:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-15/</guid>
      <description>Me: So what is one change or action, that you think would make a difference in a person&amp;rsquo;s life?
X: (After a minute of thinking) Have you ever asked or being asked by others, questions like what do you do? what are you doing? what next? what for? &amp;hellip;
Me: Yes. Almost all the time&amp;hellip;
X: If a person asks those questions to him/her self, it would make all the difference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactions of B</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2017 19:34:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-14/</guid>
      <description>Met this amazing person, Mr. X at a conference, who turned his side hustle into his career recently.
Me: Any tips on transitioning a hobby into business?
X: Yes. But first of all, know the difference between a hobby and side project.
Me: ??
X: Hobby is something you are passionate about and do it for yourself. Side project is something you are passionate about, but do it for community, people, the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leadership Ft Dashavatar</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/posts/leadership-ft-dashavatar/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 16:25:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/posts/leadership-ft-dashavatar/</guid>
      <description>There have been a lot of articles on leadership/ entrepreneurial skills these days. But you know, these qualities have been mentioned hundreds of years ago. In fact, the hidden goal of ‘Bhagavatam’ from Hindu mythology (Ten forms of Vishnu) might be to explain these qualities, in a filmy style, though. I would like to explain what each avatar is trying to portray and how they are relevant in today&amp;rsquo;s world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactions of B</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 18:40:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-13/</guid>
      <description>Interaction with stranger, X with a camera at a coffee shop
Me : you seem to be a great photographer.
X (with attitude) : You see my friend, There are no great photographers, just great photos.
Me : wow! that itself says how good photographer you are. Can I have look at your snaps?
X : huh well&amp;hellip;It&amp;rsquo;s my friends camera. He&amp;rsquo;ll be coming in 5 min. And I&amp;rsquo;m not a photographer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactions of B</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 18:40:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-12/</guid>
      <description>Interaction with a Lyft driver, Ms. X, as soon as I got into the car and greeted her with big smile and a happy face.
X: Wow! you seem to be very happy.
Me: Yeah. It is a bright day&amp;hellip; &amp;hellip; (continued discussing about random topics for some time ) &amp;hellip; X: You know, we don&amp;rsquo;t get to see a lot of happy faces in DC. People are always serious, sad or looking into phones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactions of B</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2017 18:40:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-11/</guid>
      <description>Interaction with an amazing professor of Philosophy, Ms. X, while waiting for pizza.
Me: So, I was reading this book from Simon Sinek, recently and was wondering how, from Napoleon Hill to Simon Sinek, everyone talks about the importance of Defining Your Purpose. Would Love to know your thoughts on it?
X: Yes. Defining your why is the most important step for anything. Relationships, career, organizations, life, &amp;hellip;
For example, You can have the fastest car in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A note from Bargav</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2017 21:03:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-25/</guid>
      <description>Occasionally, we should keep talking with our Younger Selves. They have great stories, dreams, commitments and advice that help find our true selves again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactions of B</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 18:40:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-10/</guid>
      <description>Not exactly a stranger, A very good friend of mine - Mr. X, A young entrepreneur, own a digital marketing agency.
Me: How is life going?
X: Life has been very forgiving &amp;amp; really made the last few years easy. Expanding company across other cities.
Me: Cool! &amp;lsquo;Life has been forgiving and easy&amp;rsquo;, good to hear that line when most of us were complaining &amp;lsquo;it sucks! &#39;
X: Probably MBA effect or really our talent - but really doing good compared to competition &amp;amp; many others of same age group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A note from Bargav</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-24/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 20:56:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-24/</guid>
      <description>Happiness and fulfillment are two different things. Anyone can be happy. It&amp;rsquo;s a state of mind. It&amp;rsquo;s a choice that one can make and be happy in seconds.
On the other hand, fulfillment is rare and precious. One need to work, follow his passion, contribute, help, succeed to be fulfilled. It takes years of dedicated hard work and commitment for just seconds of feeling fulfilled.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ravananugraha</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/posts/ravananugraha/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 01:07:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/posts/ravananugraha/</guid>
      <description>Raavana, Overconfident and obsessed with his powers, once wanted to meet Shiva but Nandhi (Shiva&amp;rsquo;s gatekeeper) denies his entry to Mt. Kailash.
Enraged by this, Raavana starts uprooting the mountain. To keep him in check, Shiva pushes the Mt. Khailas down, with his feet, trapping Raavana underneath it.
Without losing hope and being determined to live, Raavana spends next few years, trying to impress Shiva, by singing various hymns (Shiva Tandava Stotra, was result of the same), while being trapped under the mountain and using all his energy to prevent it from crushing him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A note from Bargav</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 20:56:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-23/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t aim at success. The more you aim at it and make it a target, the more you are going to miss it.
For success, like happiness, cannot be pursued; it must ensue, and it only does so as the unintended side effect of one&amp;rsquo;s personal dedication to a cause greater than oneself or as the by-product of one&amp;rsquo;s surrender to a person other than oneself. Happiness must happen, and the same holds for success: you have to let it happen by not caring about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactions of B</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 18:39:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-9/</guid>
      <description>Mr. X, A Developer, Guitarist, Writer, Photographer, Entrepreneur, Boxer, Stocks &amp;hellip; (Not a beginner, Successful in all those fields)
Me : wow! , So how were you able to master all these skills?
X : I didn&amp;rsquo;t master all those skills, I master the basics and that too not all at once.
Me : oh! Could you be more specific? please.
X : Okay! let me explain.
Imagine you didn&amp;rsquo;t knew how to read english.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A note from Bargav</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-22/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 20:56:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-22/</guid>
      <description> Ever tried? Ever failed?
No matter,
Try again. Fail again. Fail better.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A note from Bargav</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-21/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 20:56:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-21/</guid>
      <description> A good leader takes care of people who take care of people who &amp;hellip; take care of people who take care of results. - Simon Sinek
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactions of B</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 18:39:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-8/</guid>
      <description>A teenage girl X, heavy fan of Marvel universe.
Me : So what&amp;rsquo;s your favorite quote from the recent Spider Man?
X : It&amp;rsquo;s when Tony Stark says &amp;ldquo;Cap would have kicked your a** if he wanted to. &amp;quot;
Me : ??
X : Yeah! I Love Captain America.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactions of B</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2017 10:54:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-7/</guid>
      <description>A middle aged entreprenuer, X, who own a franchise restaurant in DC.
Me: How were you able to take such a risk ?
X : Let me ask you a question. How do you commute to work?
Me : I Drive.
X : You know that there is a 5% chance of you meeting with an accident and 55% if you were texting and driving.
Me : Yes. Whats up with that?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactions of B</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 18:39:48 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-6/</guid>
      <description>Met a young person X, at a store, with a 2-3 month growing beard, and he, constantly rubbing his fingers at one area of the beard
Me : Don&amp;rsquo;t do that bro. In long run, it might form patches. If you want, use full hand/ four fingers together, rub it over top.
X : Growing beard isn&amp;rsquo;t as easy as you think buddy. Try to grow it, you will then understand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FirstNet</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/projects/firstnet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2017 14:53:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/projects/firstnet/</guid>
      <description>The FirstNet mission is to deploy, operate, maintain, and improve the first high-speed, nationwide wireless broadband network dedicated to public safety.
This website is front facing , first step for the experience. It is implemented in drupal8, using panels and layout modules. This site is robust, secure and 508 Accessibility Compliant.
Project URL: https://www.firstnet.com/
Technologies Used : Drupal, Jenkins, Acquia, Amazon AWS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A note from Bargav</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2017 20:39:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-20/</guid>
      <description>Elagaina brathakali ante elagola brathikeyachu, Gaani ilage brathakali ante, veelu padadhu ee samajam lo.
 English: If we want to just live, we can live anyway. But if we want to live our way, on our terms, on our set of principles, the society won&amp;rsquo;t let you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A note from Bargav</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2017 20:39:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-19/</guid>
      <description>&amp;quot; Kanneelu kaariste kaadu, chamata chindestene charitra rayagalav. &amp;quot; - Sri Sri
 English:
 &amp;quot; The world is changed by your example, not by your opinion.&amp;quot; - Paulo Coelho
 #SriSri #PauloCoelho #TheAlchemist #quotes #inspiration</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A note from Bargav</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2017 20:39:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-18/</guid>
      <description>There are two types of people in this world.
if (condition) { ........ } &amp;amp;&amp;amp; if (condition) { ......... } </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Architectural Adventures</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/projects/architectural-adventures/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2016 14:32:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/projects/architectural-adventures/</guid>
      <description>Architectural Adventures is the official travel program of The American Institute of Architects, offering first-rate experiences in breathtaking destinations across the globe.
This is implemented during my job at AIA. It follows the same architecture and principles as that of the the previous project.
Project URL: https://www.architecturaladventures.org/
Technologies Used : Drupal, EmberJS, NodeJs, ElasticSearch, Travis-CI, Github, Amazon AWS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The American Institure of Architects</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/projects/the-american-institure-of-architects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2016 19:00:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/projects/the-american-institure-of-architects/</guid>
      <description>[comment]: # (Project should contain Summary, Description, Repo and Live urls, Screenshot or demo video and Tutorials( if any.))
The American Institute of Architects is a professional organization for architects in the United States. I feel privileged to work for this organization. As a web developer there, from 2015-2016, we built this website, using Drupal 8 and EmberJS.
This project is one of early adopters of &amp;lsquo;Progressive Decoupled&amp;rsquo; architecture. We made use Drupal8&amp;rsquo;s REST API and Ember Datastore and Ember fastboot to achieve this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A note from Bargav</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2016 20:39:22 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-17/</guid>
      <description>The society we live in, the beliefs we have,
the relationships we surround ourselves with,
our norms, our dreams, our lives, &amp;hellip;
An honest illusion or a deceptive truth? — feeling philosophical.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A note from Bargav</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2016 20:39:18 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-16/</guid>
      <description>I hate programming
I hate programming
I hate programming
It works!!!!
I love programming</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A note from Bargav</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2016 20:33:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-15/</guid>
      <description>That moment, you spend 2 hours of your time researching, how to eat tidy, with a full beard and mustache. 😎
Here are few quick tips for fellow bearded men
 Drink using straws or Bottles with narrow necks. Take smaller bites. Prefer using forks and knifes. Use napkins. The pocket napkins and moustache curling seem to be the most socially acceptable options. Say No to junk foods that leave crumbs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A note from Bargav</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2016 20:33:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-14/</guid>
      <description>One that know &amp;lsquo;why&amp;rsquo; can figure out a thousand &amp;lsquo;hows&amp;rsquo;.
One that only know what, needs to be told, &amp;lsquo;how&amp;rsquo;.
RandomThought inspired from Man&amp;rsquo;s search for meaning by Viktor Frankl</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A note from Bargav</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2016 20:33:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-13/</guid>
      <description> &amp;ldquo;It isn&amp;rsquo;t the mountains ahead that wear you down. It&amp;rsquo;s the pebble in your shoe.&amp;rdquo; - Muhammad Ali
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A note from Bargav</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 20:32:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-12/</guid>
      <description>Talking about our problems is one of our greatest addictions. Break the habit. Talk about your joys.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2015 20:24:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/about/</guid>
      <description>About Me Hi! I am Bargav. I develop websites and help organizations establish their digital presence. I like sharing knowledge and inspirations, and having deep conversations with people.
Interests | Philosophy | Technical | Contact
Interests  Love jeeps and slow driving, exploring new places. Interested in photography - capturing candid expressions and crucial moments. Like mixing philosophy, mythology, movies, cartoons, technology and everyday life. Always up for discussion over a beer!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Comment Policy</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/comment-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2015 20:24:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/comment-policy/</guid>
      <description>Comment Policy Keep it civil We’re going to get into the thick of a lot of heated discussions and that’s okay. These discussions often entail topics that we all personally care a lot about and will passionately defend. But in order for discussions to thrive, we need to remember to criticize ideas, not people.
So, remember to avoid:
 name-calling ad hominem attacks Responding to a post’s tone instead of its actual content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A note from Bargav</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2015 20:32:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-11/</guid>
      <description>This is something everyone must realize.
There is not much truth in the holy books.
Gita, Quran, Bible, &amp;hellip;are written from authors point of view. They are not the source of truth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A note from Bargav</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Sep 2015 20:07:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-10/</guid>
      <description>Society is a strange sanctuary. A sanctuary where,
Little birds are not allowed to leave their nest, but expected to fly as they are young.
Little does the young birds know, their wings have been tied.
Limitless desires to fly high across, but are confined to fly in limits.
Desperate to stand out, but compelled to fly with the flock.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A note from Bargav</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2015 20:07:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-9/</guid>
      <description>That moment, when you comment something intellectual &amp;amp; sarcastic on someone&amp;rsquo;s post and they don&amp;rsquo;t actually get it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactions of B</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2015 18:39:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-5/</guid>
      <description>Conversation with a middle aged entrepreneur X (currently working in US), who had plans to set up a company in Vizag.
X : I should probably look for another city. Who would setup a company in a cyclone prone area? It&amp;rsquo;s dream of &amp;lsquo;IT hub&amp;rsquo; will be a dream.
Me: Where else would you find people, whose spirits aren&amp;rsquo;t deterred even by such destruction?
where else would you find people that help everyone in the team, even if it&amp;rsquo;s not their job?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactions of B</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2015 09:31:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-4/</guid>
      <description>Interaction with a Stranger X, in metro to DC
Me : So, what are you planning to visit today in DC?
X : White House
Me: Seriously ? But that&amp;rsquo;s a pretty boring one.
X : Look kid, journeys are not about monuments/places. It&amp;rsquo;s about people and fun. White house is boring, but the park next to it isn&amp;rsquo;t.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A note from Bargav</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2015 20:07:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-8/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;You have to dream before your dreams can come true.&amp;rdquo; - Abdul Kalam
 One statement that kept inspiring me since childhood. Thank you #AbdulKalam for being such a source of inspiration. RIP</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A note from Bargav</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2015 20:07:28 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-7/</guid>
      <description>If you are looking for a description of reality based on certainty, your expectations would be shattered.
QuantumMechanics and Life aren&amp;rsquo;t much different.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A note from Bargav</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2015 20:07:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-6/</guid>
      <description> &amp;quot; Technology has given us everything we could ever need and at same time, stolen everything we really need &amp;quot; - Richard Williams
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A note from Bargav</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 20:07:23 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-5/</guid>
      <description>Naruni lopali parunipai drushti parupaga, Talavanchi kaimodchi sishyudavu neevaithe, Nee aarthi kadaterchu aacharyudavu neeve…
*If you realize the person within you and become his student, then you are your own guru.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A note from Bargav</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2015 20:07:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-4/</guid>
      <description>Teeram telisaka, unko darini marchana?
Darulu sari aina, vere teeram cherana?
Nadakalu navena? Nadichedi nenena??
Engish: Have I changed my route, after knowing the destination? or Have I reached wrong destination, despite going on the correct route? Is it my journey? Am I the one walking?
Kudos to lyric writer - Ananth Sriram</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A note from Bargav</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2015 20:07:18 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-3/</guid>
      <description>If you want to be a photographer, don&amp;rsquo;t mind taking numerous bad clicks.
If you want to be a dancer, don&amp;rsquo;t mind performing some awkward moves.
If you want to be a singer, don&amp;rsquo;t mind messing up tunes with your voice.
If you want to be a programmer, don&amp;rsquo;t mind throwing thousands of errors.
If you want to be a cricketer, don&amp;rsquo;t mind numerous misfields and mishits.
What ever profession you choose, who ever the expert you take, they all were once amature, made thousands of silly mistakes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A note from Bargav</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2015 20:07:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-2/</guid>
      <description>Society always tries to define stereotypes and have constraints on one&amp;rsquo;s looks. May it be dark/fair tones, thick/thin body types, facial hairs, (there is even a useless book, that judge people&amp;rsquo;s character based on eyebrow lining).
Well, growing a beard some how forces me to think beyond stereotypes, look into people&amp;rsquo;s hearts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A note from Bargav</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2015 20:06:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/notes/note-1/</guid>
      <description> The idea of hiding untill you get perfect is a fool&amp;rsquo;s game. Put yourself out there, start, practice it out loud, then you get feedback and you grow.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactions of B</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2015 20:53:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-3/</guid>
      <description>Interaction with a stranger, X, who traveled more than 25 major cities all over world.
Me : You seem to travel a lot. so what&amp;rsquo;s one thing you enjoy in your journeys?
X : You know, people always wear masks. At home, at school, at work&amp;hellip; That&amp;rsquo;s nothing wrong, as they have a story and a reason behind it. But it is only during journeys, you get to see their true selfless faces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactions of B</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2015 19:39:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-2/</guid>
      <description>Interaction with a stranger, after party.
Me : You dance awesome!! I loved it.
She : Oh!! thank you. (Whispering) You know what, I&amp;rsquo;m a movie star.
Me : Really? I don&amp;rsquo;t think so.
She : In my world, I am. Don&amp;rsquo;t I?
Me : (smiling) yeah you are, in my world too. And I&amp;rsquo;m your first fan. :D
She : awww
Biscuit!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactions of B</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 11:02:28 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-1/</guid>
      <description>Encounter with an young old man X in the bus today morning.
Me : hi, good morning!
X : hi, are you wishing me good morning or just saying that it&amp;rsquo;s a good morning?
Me : wishing&amp;hellip; Hey, isn&amp;rsquo;t that Gandalf&amp;rsquo;s dialogue from Lord of the rings??
X ( smiling ) : yeah. You watch lengthy movies but lazy enough to wish properly.
Me ( smiling ) facepalm : okay! Have a Good Morning.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
