<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Interactions on Bargav Kondapu</title>
    <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Interactions on Bargav Kondapu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 19:34:19 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactions of B</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 19:34:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-18/</guid>
      <description>An interaction with Mr. X, Doctor by profession and a Social worker by heart, at the airport waiting for our flight. Discussing ways to empower people from remote/ backward areas
Me: So why do you think the majority of the people that are hunger-stricken or poor unable to think big?
X: Okay! Tell me are you a &amp;lsquo;Glass is half-full&amp;rsquo; person or &amp;lsquo; Glass is half-empty&amp;rsquo; person?
Me: &amp;lsquo;Half-full&amp;rsquo; may be!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactions of B</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 19:36:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-17/</guid>
      <description>Wrong type of Audience! This interaction has got me thinking for a long time, and would like to know more of your thoughts on this.
Me: So what do you think is the problem with helpful articles, inspirations or advices on social media.
X: There is no problem with those articles, but the problem is with such articles reaching wrong audience. and people being inspired from sources that are not relevant to them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactions of B</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 19:34:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-16/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t usually get offended or irritated, but interactions like these, make me feel uncomfortable.
As you might already know, we are establishing a web-development firm and is currently looking for more projects. Met X, who is opening a new shop and called me to discuss his branding and development needs.
&amp;hellip;
After a lengthy discussion on how we can improve his shop&amp;rsquo;s digital footprint.
X: So, how much would you charge?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactions of B</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 19:34:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-15/</guid>
      <description>Me: So what is one change or action, that you think would make a difference in a person&amp;rsquo;s life?
X: (After a minute of thinking) Have you ever asked or being asked by others, questions like what do you do? what are you doing? what next? what for? &amp;hellip;
Me: Yes. Almost all the time&amp;hellip;
X: If a person asks those questions to him/her self, it would make all the difference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactions of B</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2017 19:34:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-14/</guid>
      <description>Met this amazing person, Mr. X at a conference, who turned his side hustle into his career recently.
Me: Any tips on transitioning a hobby into business?
X: Yes. But first of all, know the difference between a hobby and side project.
Me: ??
X: Hobby is something you are passionate about and do it for yourself. Side project is something you are passionate about, but do it for community, people, the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactions of B</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 18:40:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-13/</guid>
      <description>Interaction with stranger, X with a camera at a coffee shop
Me : you seem to be a great photographer.
X (with attitude) : You see my friend, There are no great photographers, just great photos.
Me : wow! that itself says how good photographer you are. Can I have look at your snaps?
X : huh well&amp;hellip;It&amp;rsquo;s my friends camera. He&amp;rsquo;ll be coming in 5 min. And I&amp;rsquo;m not a photographer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactions of B</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 18:40:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-12/</guid>
      <description>Interaction with a Lyft driver, Ms. X, as soon as I got into the car and greeted her with big smile and a happy face.
X: Wow! you seem to be very happy.
Me: Yeah. It is a bright day&amp;hellip; &amp;hellip; (continued discussing about random topics for some time ) &amp;hellip; X: You know, we don&amp;rsquo;t get to see a lot of happy faces in DC. People are always serious, sad or looking into phones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactions of B</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2017 18:40:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-11/</guid>
      <description>Interaction with an amazing professor of Philosophy, Ms. X, while waiting for pizza.
Me: So, I was reading this book from Simon Sinek, recently and was wondering how, from Napoleon Hill to Simon Sinek, everyone talks about the importance of Defining Your Purpose. Would Love to know your thoughts on it?
X: Yes. Defining your why is the most important step for anything. Relationships, career, organizations, life, &amp;hellip;
For example, You can have the fastest car in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactions of B</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 18:40:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-10/</guid>
      <description>Not exactly a stranger, A very good friend of mine - Mr. X, A young entrepreneur, own a digital marketing agency.
Me: How is life going?
X: Life has been very forgiving &amp;amp; really made the last few years easy. Expanding company across other cities.
Me: Cool! &amp;lsquo;Life has been forgiving and easy&amp;rsquo;, good to hear that line when most of us were complaining &amp;lsquo;it sucks! &amp;lsquo;
X: Probably MBA effect or really our talent - but really doing good compared to competition &amp;amp; many others of same age group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactions of B</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 18:39:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-9/</guid>
      <description>Mr. X, A Developer, Guitarist, Writer, Photographer, Entrepreneur, Boxer, Stocks &amp;hellip; (Not a beginner, Successful in all those fields)
Me : wow! , So how were you able to master all these skills?
X : I didn&amp;rsquo;t master all those skills, I master the basics and that too not all at once.
Me : oh! Could you be more specific? please.
X : Okay! let me explain.
Imagine you didn&amp;rsquo;t knew how to read english.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactions of B</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 18:39:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-8/</guid>
      <description>A teenage girl X, heavy fan of Marvel universe.
Me : So what&amp;rsquo;s your favorite quote from the recent Spider Man?
X : It&amp;rsquo;s when Tony Stark says &amp;ldquo;Cap would have kicked your a** if he wanted to. &amp;ldquo;
Me : ??
X : Yeah! I Love Captain America.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactions of B</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2017 10:54:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-7/</guid>
      <description>A middle aged entreprenuer, X, who own a franchise restaurant in DC.
Me: How were you able to take such a risk ?
X : Let me ask you a question. How do you commute to work?
Me : I Drive.
X : You know that there is a 5% chance of you meeting with an accident and 55% if you were texting and driving.
Me : Yes. Whats up with that?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactions of B</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 18:39:48 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-6/</guid>
      <description>Met a young person X, at a store, with a 2-3 month growing beard, and he, constantly rubbing his fingers at one area of the beard
Me : Don&amp;rsquo;t do that bro. In long run, it might form patches. If you want, use full hand/ four fingers together, rub it over top.
X : Growing beard isn&amp;rsquo;t as easy as you think buddy. Try to grow it, you will then understand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactions of B</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2015 18:39:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-5/</guid>
      <description>Conversation with a middle aged entrepreneur X (currently working in US), who had plans to set up a company in Vizag.
X : I should probably look for another city. Who would setup a company in a cyclone prone area? It&amp;rsquo;s dream of &amp;lsquo;IT hub&amp;rsquo; will be a dream.
Me: Where else would you find people, whose spirits aren&amp;rsquo;t deterred even by such destruction?
where else would you find people that help everyone in the team, even if it&amp;rsquo;s not their job?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactions of B</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2015 09:31:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-4/</guid>
      <description>Interaction with a Stranger X, in metro to DC
Me : So, what are you planning to visit today in DC?
X : White House
Me: Seriously ? But that&amp;rsquo;s a pretty boring one.
X : Look kid, journeys are not about monuments/places. It&amp;rsquo;s about people and fun. White house is boring, but the park next to it isn&amp;rsquo;t.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactions of B</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2015 20:53:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-3/</guid>
      <description>Interaction with a stranger, X, who traveled more than 25 major cities all over world.
Me : You seem to travel a lot. so what&amp;rsquo;s one thing you enjoy in your journeys?
X : You know, people always wear masks. At home, at school, at work&amp;hellip; That&amp;rsquo;s nothing wrong, as they have a story and a reason behind it. But it is only during journeys, you get to see their true selfless faces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactions of B</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2015 19:39:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-2/</guid>
      <description>Interaction with a stranger, after party.
Me : You dance awesome!! I loved it.
She : Oh!! thank you. (Whispering) You know what, I&amp;rsquo;m a movie star.
Me : Really? I don&amp;rsquo;t think so.
She : In my world, I am. Don&amp;rsquo;t I?
Me : (smiling) yeah you are, in my world too. And I&amp;rsquo;m your first fan. :D
She : awww
Biscuit!!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactions of B</title>
      <link>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2014 11:02:28 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bargavkondapu.com/interactions/interaction-1/</guid>
      <description>Encounter with an young old man X in the bus today morning.
Me : hi, good morning!
X : hi, are you wishing me good morning or just saying that it&amp;rsquo;s a good morning?
Me : wishing&amp;hellip; Hey, isn&amp;rsquo;t that Gandalf&amp;rsquo;s dialogue from Lord of the rings??
X ( smiling ) : yeah. You watch lengthy movies but lazy enough to wish properly.
Me ( smiling ) facepalm : okay! Have a Good Morning.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>